Hello Hello Viewers Welcome to my YouTube
channel friends ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company Today
I will tell you all the things about this company that
you should know before investing
If you want to do stock buying then the
first thing you should
see is what you will get to see in this video
and due to the news that
people are coming to YouTube and searching for videos
that ICC Bank has reduced its stake
in IPL Om Bird from just 3.6 percent, I will also use this news
here regularly and tell you
why the bank has done such a thing here and the
stake that it has here, so first of all I would like to
tell you that
you have invested in a very good company
here, you do
not need to panic at all, first of all you should
worship yourself and after that you can see the rest of the things, so
come to the stopper
company but what is on your mind ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company was
stakes in twelve joint ventures
between ICICI Bank one of the many
India's closest banks and financial
holdings limited  Affairs 24 company in
Toronto, Canada. So ICICI Lombard
is a company of Ubleeps, that is, Mafi Bank and
Financial Holdings.
This means that the share of both the companies is
completely within Salumbar. Okay, so this is done.
In the general insurance, the
promoters or the
owners of these companies, who are they? Citibank and
Israel Feature. Fairfax Financial
Holdings Limited, which is a
company owned by ICICI Lombard. After that, you should see
which products does ICICI Lombard General Insurance sell here
or what are their products? So, first of all,
you have to see that it does
room but motor insurance.
In this number, health insurance is a factor of health insurance, so you can understand that Salumbar is there,
after that, travel insurance, home
insurance, recent events insurance,
property, nurture, summer insurance and
relatives insurance. Front and crop insurance.
So, whatever comes under insurance,
here you will be able to see that ICICI Lombard covers all those insurances.
If you do
not know anything here  Regarding the mission, let me
tell you here that the renewal,
shoots etc. which are
dipped on the ships etc. that go in the sea, it also covers that,
apart from that the professional means which is related to
agriculture, it also
covers here, travel insurance whether
you are
going or by plane here
towards Katrina, so if you are going by any means, then your
travel expenses on that are
covered here, which
you should take here, this company is very
good, you will see it covering here,
in the property end, you will understand
that if there is your factory etc., then everything is
covered, so
they have a very good product portfolio, which means you should
not do anything without it, after that let us
see their partners etc., then
5025 hospitals are part of them and 7800 and
partner eleven, that is, the settings etc. that happen inside the hospital, for that
you have their 5025 hospitals along with their  Meaning,
their products will be given to you there, you will be able to use
their entire company
there and if there is any
dispute, then
you will be able to get the work done here in 7800 garages, on the
basis of their insurance, let us
see that the highest claim settlement
ratio in India, which
is the Prem Tatva receiver till the end of 2019, whenever you
talk about this in MS Word, quickly look in it,
you have got 986 health insurance claims
settled and they have settled 19.14 personal motor
insurance claims,
so by looking at your claim settlement history, you will be
able to understand how the company is, okay,
after that, see the awards given to the company,
Golden Peacock Award which they got
in 2016, after that, they got here,
then Intellect Insurance
Award which they got in 2017, after that,
if you see how number General Insurance is the
first Indian company divided with IS to
prevent guru in 2018, then this is the first
company which has got IS as Secretary  1000,
what is this award, I mean I don't know, it could be a very
big award, but is this
award given only to them in India,
in 2018, this happened, their
awards etc. and the company says what work it does,
I have explained it to you,
after that let's come to the stock, on 19th June 2020, on
NSC, in this project, the
market of the stock is above Rs 1271, if we
talk about 57 thousand 556 crores, then
15.23, it deals stop at PE multiple of 50, if we
talk about Diya Acid, then it is
not good, here you will see withdrawal, it will
show a gain of 0.5%, if you
look at the stock, it is around 1440 and if we
talk about backwards, what is the price band of ₹5,
this is called officer, so the circle stock, it will go
up by 20%, it will go to 2075
maximum, after that it will take
some rest there, it will go down, then after going down, it will go to 20 questions  After going
there, he will take some rest. The
circuit is of 15 minutes, so that is an
anchor of 20 questions. After that, see the soil in
pattern. Such is the patrolling pattern of Lombard General Insurance.
Here you will
see that the
percentage of the bank is 5.8, which has reduced the
trend to point to point. This
notification has been given by the bank.
If we talk about App and Mutual Fund, then Reliance has kept a
stake of 10.41 percent here. If we talk about
FD or portfolio investment, then
553 percent full investors have
bought this point three nine percent stake here. After that,
we should definitely see
how much the company does. So, if you look at the
stand roadways bus stand album total gift
or house on the company, you will see a total gift of Rs 485 crore,
which is a secured role and this
Jhalyavar is formed, it comes till March 2019. So the
stand-alone loan which is being done
till March 2019 is Rs 485 crore, which is a
secured loan.  This is all
you
need to know about the stock and the company. After that, I will bring you to the stock chart as well.
If you look at the 5-
day chart of the stock,
Vikram Bhai, you see, the
5-minute high is around Rs 1380 and if you look at the current price, then from
this point onwards, a ₹100 note is worth up to ₹2
lakhs, so on June 16, the
topper Juhi Hijab Workshop of Rs 1379 has been
placed around the stock of the people. Due to this news, so
look at the knife there, by doing point name and
person, you are getting work hard to spoil the
Lombard General Insurance Company. If you
look at the Pichamnki chart,
this top 10 is correct. Okay, if you
look at the sentence chart above the Matka chart, then the staff is given a nine to nine by
licking St. Paul's David Warner. After that, if you see
what was the situation inside the stock after listing  If you
look at it, then the ATC
point is that year, that is, after the listing,
you will press a special person, which will give you the
result by giving it to the shop and the lip-syncing
thing is not very old, 29th
September 2007,
in the stock list of Jhaal, Papa who looted the
pregnancy, you will be able to see the Lord God,
29th September 2017, 29th September 2017, this
stock was entered on this net,
till the price, there was not so much job, so if you
look at the campaign and price from rupees, then the
stock came to 1271, the people who pleased, will
you see the stock above, here you will see that it has happened, the
meaning of the stock should
go above the stop, whatever had to go and here if
you look at the trading situation on NSC, then on
19th June 2020, if you look at the trading situation on these ACs, then
2 crore 70 lakh 38
thousand 404 stocks have been traded and if you
look at the medium and quantity, then 68.30 is
showing on the developed quality or web browser of Prasanna
and  The quantity is 1 crore 84000 861 crore
and delivery has been taken on 1 crore 84 lakh 86 thousand 131
talkies, so you take
care,
secondly, if something happens, from this you will be able to see
that people have
shown a lot of trust in the company and the previous order of Ashok was
placed after exhaustion on 19 March 2019 and High
Captain was placed on 26 December 2019 at ₹14.40, there is a network here, take a
look at the trading situation on BSE once, what would have happened on Desi on
19 June 2020,
trading was done on 7 lakh 81 thousand 819 north posts
and the message 447000 134 talkies have been
taken delivery here, if you take it out in percentage
then you will see the center sadalbal quantity
in BSE, there is 68th person in Nashik, so
see, now I would
like to give you a little bit of my own opinion here, if you want to
buy then take it, otherwise you do
n't have much to say  I have said as much as I had to tell you,
see friends, this stock
is such a stock, this stock is ICICI
Lombard General SS Stock, which is
a slightly requested term in its field, that this is the
first thing, that is, if we
look at the stock market from the perspective of the stock market, then there is no computer in the market, there is
someone in the president, they do not have a computer
and if you ask
how the company will generate returns for you in the coming days, then
in the coming days, definitely they will
generate good returns, but
before adding such a stock to your portfolio, you have to convince yourself
that I am talking about this stock for at least 10 years,
that you
should adopt this study, if you ask you that brother, there is a
lot of pressure for a long time, yes, I will
tell you that much, now I will
give you my opinion, now the rest you have to decide yourself, for
how many days you will
talk and buy, see, if you panic too much on the stocks which are good stocks
and
if you
relax too much by mixing some small stocks, then you will not be
able to make money, you have come to the stock market, you are
a bank here  It is not an FD that means the
interest you will get here will be on the returns, there will be
no news etc. If you get any news, even
then it will not make any difference to your returns.
This does not happen.
In the stock market, you can take any stock for a year, then the
next year, whatever you did
not get this year, cross that
and the next year,
if you add the returns of both, then they
make a detox. But before investing, you should
see everything.
After signing up, if you see brother,
what should you do, he will
ask thousands of questions to the people at the stop. This should not happen.
Whatever you have to see, whatever you
understand, you should
see it before investing. You should understand before missing.
After investing, you should
not tamper with anything. If you
invest in the stocks of good companies, then it will be different.
History is the witness that the
stocks of good companies have never disappointed you.
This question will come to your mind that if the curd is
half a teaspoon, then it has not given good returns. If you
look at it personally, it has
not given an editor, Twitter gives a good bonus.  It has also been
given, makeup is done a little bit and
give time, this app will also give you returns, I will
take it from Roy here, so
for example, I have taken Tika
ABC, it is a very good source and here let's
talk about age, let's talk about height,
in the first number you definitely or
if you have taken Kharbe on which you have taken it for
680 instead of
1440, whatever
price you have taken it for, if
you are able to fold it, then you should
definitely fold it, the company
can slow you down a lot in the coming days because if asked,
why, I mean, the demand for the field in which this company works will be
very high,
if we talk about life insurance,
if you see,
ten, twenty, twenty-five years ago, people did
not get life insurance done in their name,
but now if you see, the vibrations that
everyone gets it done will give you and their
product is Zee channel, horticulture development, motor
insurance, home insurance, today all the questions are there,
if you see, people are getting health
insurance, people are getting this  Gradually, I am
understanding that if they go home for Christmas, then
their family
members who were there will
get the money, but if there is a balance, then
they will get this money, their savings,
we will not have to lose out on the service and their
financial situation will
not be affected much, so people are also taking help missions
and Hindu Saka, which is an international, there is a lot of
anti-national need in India,
we are already taking it in India and if we talk about
property insurance factories which do
supreme jokers etc. then they will get it done
and what is the problem with these companies,
the problem you can face after investing in these companies,
if you
have to pay a big plan then there is a problem with them, so
they have had to pay the claim 12 times, so
this can also be a problem, but this does
not happen in most of the companies and
how much do you have to pay, that we mostly give
them so much in the field in which they are, that is,
except for the PIMPL, the
rest of the property or practice  Etc., they are
not much useful for them,
so it is okay to give oil to the
media company, hence it is a
company for settling tips, it is a profit making
company, then if there is investment then you can stay invested
and if you
see, if you look at the company in 2019, till 31 March 2019, then the
company has
set 26.55 million followers on it and it has already done so
and a total of 1.6 million
Flamingos have been served, so if you
can see, it sells two crush 22 crore 65 lakh policies, so
you should invest daily in good companies and should not panic,
but as I
say in this video, do
not invest here after listening to me,
you have to do your own research, you have to do that much
role, after that you will be involved in it,
friends, I have explained to you here what you should do
here, how is the stock such a
company, if you have
any question in your mind here and that is a real question,
then you  Definitely ask by commenting
and you can also tell us how you liked the video by
commenting here. Thank you friends, I will
not say much, the video is very long,
Jai Hind.